Found 3 connected devices:
  Windows (desktop) тАв windows тАв windows-x64    тАв Microsoft Windows [Version 10.0.19045.6466]
  Chrome (web)      тАв chrome  тАв web-javascript тАв Google Chrome 146.0.7680.178
  Edge (web)        тАв edge    тАв web-javascript тАв Microsoft Edge 146.0.3856.84

Device R58MA0NCNGT is not authorized.
You might need to check your device for an authorization dialog.

Run "flutter emulators" to list and start any available device emulators.

If you expected another device to be detected, please run "flutter doctor" to diagnose potential issues. You may also try increasing the time to wait for connected devices with the "--device-timeout" flag. Visit https://flutter.dev/setup/ for troubleshooting tips.
